http://www.artgallery.wa.gov.au/privacy

Kedela wer kalyakoorl ngalak Wadjak boodjak yaak.
Today and always, we stand on the traditional land of the Whadjuk Noongar people.
Overview
The Art Gallery WA does not collect personal information about visitors to our website unless you choose to provide that information to us, nor do we sell, exchange or release your personal information to any third parties. We define "personal information" as information which identifies you as an individual, or from which your identity can be reasonably ascertained. Your home address, home telephone number and e-mail address are examples of personal information.
Information Collected and Stored Automatically
If you visit our website, we automatically gather and store the following information about your visit so that we can track the use of our Website in order to make improvements. This information is stored and used in the aggregate only, and is not used to contact you personally or store any personal information:
The IP address from which you access our website
The type of browser and operating system used to access our website
The date and time you access our site
The pages, files, documents and links that you visit
Cookies
In addition to information collected automatically, we may also collect cookies, which are small pieces of information sent to your browser by a website that you visit. Cookies are used to track usage patterns, traffic trends and customer behaviour, as well as to record other information from the Website. When you register on the Website, cookies also allow us to save information so that you will not have to re-enter it the next time you visit. Many content adjustments and customer service improvements are made based on the data derived from cookies. Information that we collect from cookies will not be used to create profiles of users and only will be used in aggregate form.
You may set your browser to refuse cookies from any website that you visit. If you so choose, you may still gain access to most of the website, but you may not be able to take advantage of some of the interactive elements offered.
Web Measurement Services
A large proportion of pages on our websites are coded with Google Analytics software and tracking pixels.
The Google Analytics software stores a cookie in your browser, which contains a unique identifier, and sends information to Google Analytics. This helps us understand which areas of the site are popular, site duration and site referrals. We do not and will not combine any data collected by Google Analytics with any personal information. Please refer to Google's Privacy Policy for more information.
In addition, we are also running a tracking pixel via Yahoo 7 and facebook. This helps the WA Museum to better understand the success of our marketing campaigns on external websites, and to re-evaluate our strategies where necessary. We do not combine this data with any personal information that users may provide. Please refer to Yahoo 7's privacy policy for further information.
AGWA’s website will only collect personal information which you knowingly and voluntarily provide by, for example, sending emails, completing membership forms, registering for classes, events, or other programs, responding to surveys or ordering merchandise.
If you provide us with personal information, we will normally respond to your inquiry, request or order. We may also contact you to provide information about AGWA activities, programs, membership and development opportunities, products and special events that may interest you. We will never share your name or information outside AGWA unless you affirmatively authorise us to do so by opting-in.
When we send you such information by email, you will always have an immediate opportunity to decline further communication. Please use the contact specified in the email so that we can remove you from the list that contains your name. If you are uncertain about whom to contact, you may contact our webmaster at admin@artgallery.wa.gov.au.
© 2020 Art Gallery WA All rights reserved.
Back to top
Site Map
What's on
What's Next
What's happened
Awards
Visit
AGWA Shop
Artwork Credits
Kedela wer kalyakoorl ngalak Wadjak boodjak yaak.
Today and always, we stand on the traditional land of the Whadjuk Noongar people.
© 2020 Art Gallery WA
All rights reserved.
N
GALLERY OPEN
Wed to Mon 10am-5pm
Closed Tuesdays, Good Friday, Anzac Day and Christmas Day
Entry is free, donations welcomed. Special exhibitions may incur a ticket fee.
Site Map
What's on
What's Next
What's happened
Awards
Visit
AGWA Shop
Stay in WA
Artwork Credits
AGWA acknowledges Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander people as the traditional owners of Country throughout Australia and we pay respect to Elders past and present.
Search
